They stole his future. Now he's taking it back.
The Adjustment Bureau is a science fiction, thriller,
romance film directed by George Nolfi.
A man glimpses the future Fate has planned for him – and
chooses to fight for his own destiny.
Battling the powerful Adjustment Bureau across, under and through the streets of New York,
he risks his destined greatness to be with the only woman he's ever loved.
David Norris, played by Matt Damon.
Elise Sellas, played by Emily Blunt.
Richardson, played by John Slattery.
Harry Mitchell, played by Anthony Mackie.
Charlie Traynor, played by Michael Kelly.
Thompson, played by Terence Stamp.
The Adjustment Bureau is a 2011 American science fiction romantic thriller film written, directed
and co-produced by George Nolfi in his directorial debut, loosely based on Philip K.
Dick's 1954 short story "Adjustment Team".
The film stars Matt Damon, Emily Blunt, Anthony Mackie, John
Slattery, Michael Kelly, and Terence Stamp.
Its plot follows an ambitious young congressman who finds himself entranced by a beautiful
ballerina, but mysterious forces are conspiring to prevent their love affair.
The Adjustment Bureau premiered at the Ziegfeld Theatre in New York City on February 14, 2011, and
was theatrically released in the United States by Universal Pictures on March 4, 2011.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed over
$127.8 million worldwide against a $62 million budget.
It was nominated for Best Science Fiction Film and Blunt won
Best Supporting Actress at the 38th Saturn Awards.
The film explores themes of hotel, future, plan, dancer, hat.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.